The block is the gold standard, sir.
Yes, sir.
Yes, for delivery, this is on the way.
This is...
This is it.
Announcement?
You're going to announce it?
Not an announcement. Send us the stunt.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just like you did with the regular block.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Do you want me to send it out again?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It's good.
Is it in? Is it in?
I think it's spinning.
Hi. - Hi.
Good evening.
It was a little hot today, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
I thought it was going to cool down quickly.
But it's starting to get hot again.
I thought it was going to cool down at once, but now it's getting hot again.
I still can't get enough of it.
When it's hot, it makes you happy, doesn't it?
Oh, yeah?
I love it.
You like it better in the summer?
Yeah, I guess. That's why I'm like...
Sweating like a baby and drinking a lot of water.
I love it.
Heh.
I don't know, I don't like it.
Well, that's why...
I'd like to go on with the recording.
I'd like to get on with the recording.
Please join us again this week for the live broadcast.
Thank you very much.
There are a lot of words that he said to me that I remember very well.
There are a lot of words that you remember very well, aren't there?
Of course, there are things that my parents or teachers said to me that really touched my heart.
But there are also things that people have said to me that I remember very well.
Me, Mariko and Servon... we filmed together in the summer.
We waited and waited and waited and waited and waited and waited and waited and waited and waited and waited and waited and waited and waited and waited and waited and waited and waited and waited and waited and waited and waited and waited and waited.
We had a lot of drinks and ate a lot of food.
At that time...
On the way back...
Sarpong said...
I said to him...
Mariko is really a beautiful girl, isn't she?
He said...
A beautiful girl.
Wait a minute!
Wait, wait, wait.
She's a beautiful girl, isn't she?
I'm sure she's a beautiful girl.
No, I'm sure she's a beautiful girl.
It's not fair.
You're the master, aren't you?
Of course.
Why did you just tell on me?
It's not fair!
It's not like I said anything bad.
It's embarrassing.
Embarrassing compliment!
I'm not ashamed to call something beautiful.
It's not bad. I don't think it's bad.
I'm a boy, you know.
I'm a boy.
I'm a sparkling boy, but today I'm dressed like a human mirror ball, but I'm still embarrassed.
I was told by someone called “Terukoshi” that I was dressed like a wind, and I said, “Well, that's just it.
It's a conversation between guys.
Junior high? No, no, no... but I'm thinking about it.
I don't think...
It's getting weird to say this, too.
Saying “I think” is getting weird too.
No, no, no...
It's not that.
It's not like I said it to your face.
It's just something I said in passing.
That's amazing, you remember that so well.
It was about the time we were leaving.
It's really nice when you guys break up and go somewhere together, isn't it?
I'll be on location at the beach, you know...
I was on the boat with Mariko and I saw her sleeping and it's rare to see her sleeping, right?
And the way they were sleeping, they were all on the chairs because they weren't sleeping in the right place.
So, you know, you're on the boat, getting hit by the waves, you know.
So it was a little bit cute, like a father on his way to work.
That's right.
And he wasn't wearing a uniform.
That was the first time I saw him on location.
It was like I was seeing him for the first time.
We usually see you in uniform.
So it was a new experience for me.
You were a beautiful girl.
That makes me happy.
“Beautiful girl” is the highest compliment.
I'm embarrassed.
Embarrassing.
On the contrary, I'm a little embarrassed.
Why?
It's getting hot.
It's hot today.
It's so hot today.
It's slightly hot todayIt's hot todayYes, yes, yes, it's 30 hotToday it's hotToday it's hotToday it's hot, yes, yes, it's hot
It was over 30 degrees Celsius.
It's been a long time
Maybe that's why
It's been a while.
Well, well, well...
I'd like to write to you.
I'd like to say something.
I'll say this.
Where am I?
Well, Shikita... but last week... he was in Machida.
He asked me to send him some photos of the Machida area.
Thank you very much.
He asked me to check it out by next week.
So you went there.
Yes, I did.
I'm glad to hear that.
So, first of all...
I'll start with the email from the person who sent it.
Let's start with the e-mail from the person who sent it.
Mr. Fukurokun from Hachioji City, Tokyo
Thank you very much. So he sent this picture.
He sent me this picture of a shopping center.
It's like a shopping center... but this line is drawn in a way that's easy to understand.
There's a staircase in the middle, and up and down on the left and right.
So if there's a staircase in the middle, and on either side there's an ascent and a descent, it's surprising, but at a glance it looks a little traditional.
It's a little bit traditional, isn't it?
No, but when I first saw it, I really wondered where I was.
But when I first saw it, I wondered where I was... but then I saw this escalator going up and down, and there are stairs in the middle.
And this is almost the wall.
And the easiest way to see it is to zoom in.
Wait a minute.
This is the area here.
Yes, yes, yes.
You can see the parking lot in the back here.
It's a coin-operated parking lot.
I thought, “This is it.
I went there.
That picture...
That picture... wait a minute... that picture...
This is it.
This is the place.
That's right.
Oh, that's right.
This is JR
Yokohama Line
of the JR Yokohama Line.
stairs and escalator.
That means it goes up at the top of the stairs, right?
Yes, there is a Yodobashi Camera in Machida.
Heh...
And when I saw this picture again, I realized how colorful the floor was.
I've been using the Yodobashi Camera a lot.
I never realized how colorful the street I used to use used to be.
The tiles are like they are emitting light.
It's so stylish.
The tiles must have been very stylish.
Behind here is Yodo Bridge.
And there's a family restaurant on the right.
There it is!
I see it!
I don't recognize it like this, but I got it.
I see.
There it is.
I don't know, but...
You know, I'm taking my cell phone out of the street and I'm taking out a picture.
I was like, “What am I doing?
If the police find out about this...
If the police find me like this, I'll be finished.
If I do that, I'll lose my job.
But if I tell them this is what I'm doing, it'll be okay.
You'll be fine?
They've done this to me many times.
I'm sure it's fine.
I'm not going to do anything you want to see behind your back.
I'm not happy when I find it from the same angle.
I don't know why, but it makes me really happy, like I'm putting the last piece of the puzzle together.
I really want to do it! I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it!
I'd love to!
By the way...
I got another one this week.
Let's see...
Yes, that's right.
The one you sent me...
Um...
Wait a minute.
It's okay.
Thank you very much for sending us this picture of a tower mansion seen from a park in Miyamae Ward, Kawasaki City, Kanagawa Prefecture.
Yes, he sent me this.
This is it... this is it...
I don't know what this is, but it's a tower apartment
People around here know it's that place, don't they?
Musashi Kosugi
Musashi-Kosugi has a lot of models, ----, but the biggest clue is this objet d'art.
Can you understand it? I think it's in Nakahara Peace Park.
This “Three Kingdoms” game is probably a combination of a tower mansion and something like this.
Yes, that's right.
I want to make it look like a tower mansion.
That's right, isn't it?
If that's the case, then that's exactly what it is.
That's why I went there.
I thought, “This must be the place.
This is exactly what it looks like.
It's perfect.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I was very happy with this one, too.
It's like, “There it is.
Is this taken from a little bit lower?
No, it's just a little bit... so I'm trying to do a little bit of everything.
I'm trying to do a few different things, but even when I look at his picture, it doesn't look like it's from this angle. Is it big?
Yes, it's in close proximity.
I see what you mean.
This is right here, and you can see Towerman over there.
I see it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You know, it's amazing.
It's a big area.
I've been going around Kanagawa for decades.
I've been traveling around for decades.
I don't know who to talk to in Tokyo and who not to talk to in Tokyo.
I'm sure you'll know it when you hear the word “Ebisu”.
Evisu! Are you out of Ebisu? I don't know anything about the Ebisu area.
I don't know the area around Ebisu... you know, JR line, Hibiya line...
I know the area around Taco Park.
But when you get into the more secluded areas...
I don't get it.
I don't know Mr. Minister...
Well, well, well, well... maybe what's so great about you people is that when you go into the places you see... you don't understand the 23 wards.
Well, well, well, well...
You know what's great?
You've given us some good hints.
Yes, yes, yes, yes...
Yes, yes, that's why this picture, and the tower blocks...
And because you put in these objects...
So you can tell it's not there.
The hints are good.
Just the right amount of hints.
You know, if you're watching the live broadcast, you'll know it's there, right?
Hey, hey, hey...
Spoilers, spoilers, spoilers...
I mean, I could be talking about the future, but...
From the crotch.
From the crotch of that Gundam.
You can see the gap between the pears.
I thought that was a very good hint.
I think it's a very good hint.
It's a very good hint.
If you can find it...
I'd love to hear from you.
If you could send it to me, if you could send it to Mariko...
If you could send it to Mariko...
If you make it too difficult...
I might not be able to find it.
I've been trying to sell the center of Ebisu all day.
I can't go there.
It's going to be difficult.
I don't want to make it too difficult, but I don't want to make it too hard.
I don't want to be too nice.
That's right.
If you have any, I'd appreciate it if you could send them to me.
I'd love to hear from you.
This corner has been more exciting than I thought it would be.
I wonder why it's so exciting.
It's a lot of fun.
When we first started
What is this?
It's such a simple program...
or “Is there a corner for this? something like that.
When we talked about it, I was surprised.
I feel like I'm communicating directly with the viewers.
It's like, “I didn't know you were here.
That's something new and fresh.
Of course, we will continue to do this corner, but I hope it will grow.
Yes, that's right.
Various things.
Where is this place? I'd like to hold a festival or something.
Oh, I'd love to.
Somewhere big.
Like Yokohama Arena.
That's great.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Well, well, well...
And now, I have a letter for you.
This is just a small photo.
I went to renew my driver's license.
I'm sure it's a violation if you don't write “master” on your license.
I'm really sorry...
I have to renew my driver's license...
I have to renew my driver's license... but this is just a simple photo...
I have to renew my driver's license... but here's a simple picture... but this is the test center for sharks and sharks and sharks... in Shinagawa or something, right?
I'm sorry, I'm not sure how many more places there are in Tokyo.
I'm actually a former resident of Tokyo but we've only been to Fuchu.
That's why I've always wanted to take a shark test.
I've been going to see sharks to renew my driver's license for a long time.
I like sharks, so I thought the name “Shark Chart” was cool.
Cute!
So, let's see, if you're from Kanagawa, you're probably from Futamatagawa, right?
Right there.
Asahi-ku.
Around there.
I'm sure there are others.
Shark Map
I dare you.
I had a shark chart.
Yes.
With the shark chart for the proving ground.
Yeah.
Was that an emergency or a request?
Yeah, I think so, yeah, I think so.
It's an emergency.
I think it was.
A driver's license, by the way.
Mariko and I are unlicensed now.
When people say I don't have a license...
I'm doing something bad.
I don't have a mate.
I don't have a license.
I don't want to get one in the future.
I'm not...
I'm ready to take it.
But my mom said I shouldn't.
That's right.
She told me to stay in the girls' seat.
Mariko's mom seems like the type who'd go for it.
She's a go-getter.
Mariko's mom?
What do you think of her?
Pulling her daughter along.
That's right.
I have an image of her.
Yes, she does.
Yes, I do.
Yes, I do. Well, living in Tokyo...
I know what people mean when they say they don't want something.
I can understand why people say they don't want it.
Yes, I do.
It's easy.
There are so many train lines.
And there are lots of cabs.
Yes, there are.
And anyway, you need a license and a car.
It's a lot harder than you think. I don't mean to say this, but...
I was a bit of a loser back then, but I thought I'd get it right away.
But I've complained a lot to my instructor about how tough it was.
I'm sorry I quit.
That's why my instructor said... if it's so easy to get a driver's license...
If it's so easy to get a driver's license...
If it was that easy to get a driver's license... there would be people who don't appreciate it and violate the law...
You have to take it seriously.
So it's also meant to teach you that you have to be serious about it.
There was a scary guy with a perm and sunglasses like this.
wearing sunglasses like this.
I don't want to be talked to by you!
It takes a long time to get a car, and young people don't get licenses anymore.
I can understand that compared to when I was a big kid.
Just having a car in the garage costs tens of thousands of dollars a year in taxes, taxes, taxes, taxes.
And if you drive it for a while, you'll have to pay for fuel.
Of course, parking fees are fine if you live in a house, but if you live in a condo, they charge you a monthly fee.
If you live in a condominium, you have to pay a monthly fee.
Even if you don't do anything, it costs a lot of money.
That's why car sharing is so popular, isn't it?
Yes, yes, yes.
I wish they'd do something about that.
It's really hard to have a car.
If you don't do that, young people will leave.
If they don't like to drive, they won't change.
When we were young, you know...
If you didn't have a car, you couldn't afford one.
So to pick up your girlfriend with a car was one of the status quo.
Some cars didn't have power windows called “PUE” at that time.
So, you know...
Her face is a bit pallid, but...
I'm not a good-looking person, but I'm a good-looking person. Like that.
Do you want a cup of tea? Like that.
I'm just saying, you know, with power windows, you can just swoosh.
Shoo.
But the ones that don't, you can't see them from here.
It's hard on the arms, but...
It was a little embarrassing.
That was the way it was back then, you know.
That's how it was in those days.
Everyone, probably the boys...
At that time, when you turned 18, it was a normal thing.
At 16, they were driving a moped.
And the middle side...
It was normal to get a regular driver's license at 18.
Everyone got their driver's license as if they were competing with each other...
But now I hear it's different... I wonder what's going to happen now?
I'm worried. I think I'll call it quits.
We haven't talked yet. We've been talking for 20 minutes.
That much? That's true.
I thought we'd only been talking for about two minutes.
I'm sorry.
Let's finish up.
I was wondering if we could have a...
A hot springs convention.
So...
I usually introduce food...
I usually introduce food and other things.
But this time of year, it's time for hot springs, right?
I'm sure you've heard of hot springs, right?
First of all, I'd like to introduce you to the sun and the sheep.
I'm off to Kusatsu Onsen in Gunma!
The first thing you need to do is to get a good look at the hot springs in your area.
I've already got a few.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea to have a few of these on hand, but I've already had a few.
I've never been to Kusatsu.
I've never been to Kusatsu, but someone who has told me about it says the water is amazing and the ingredients are really strong.
I've never been to Kusatsu, but the people who have been there say that the water is so hot that no one ever crosses over because the ingredients are so strong.
If you don't go into the diluted water, you'll suddenly be in the hot water.
I'm just saying the same thing twice.
That's why the water is so good.
Maybe it's really good for curing people? Maybe it can heal injuries.
Maybe it's good for stiff shoulders.
You can do that, too. Like a Ryucho kind of thing.
So, Kusatsu.
And Saitama Prefecture
Asaka City, Saitama Prefecture!
Thank you very much!
I'm going to go to Unzen Onsen in Nagasaki Prefecture.
Unzen Onsen
You should go there.
I want to go there.
Souce-of-spring free-flowing hot-spring water
Souce-of-spring run-off is a carefully selected free-flowing hot-spring water.
It's cool, isn't it?
It's like a line from a period drama where the samurai are at the end and they're saying, “Carefully selected hot spring water is flowing! I'm talking about a hot spring like that.
I'm talking about the smell of sulfur, too.
The smell of sulfur was very pleasant.
The bath was so beautiful!
The hot water is amazing!
This is great!
This is nice... this is nice hot water...
It's going to be a while...
Maybe by the end of October...
I'm sure everyone will be going to the hot springs by the end of October.
It's going to get cooler.
You know...
Yes, yes, yes.
By the way...
Where was the hot spring? Where was the hot spring? Where was the hot spring?
I don't know... where I've been, where I've been...
I don't know where I've been... and I haven't even been to a good spring or anything... but where have I been?
Hakone.
Hakone?
It's so close by and yet there's such good hot water coming out of the ground.
It's a really great place.
My own party
I'm sorry.
It's okay, please talk.
I was born in Suwa, Nagano Prefecture, not Tokyo.
I was born not in Tokyo, but in Kami Suwa in Nagano Prefecture.
I was born in Kami-Suwa, Nagano Prefecture, not in Tokyo.
There are footbaths at train stations and other places.
Each household pays a certain amount of money to the city hall.
If you pay a little money to the city hall, you can get hot spring water.
It's amazing!
The water supply is like a tap.
So it's like a hot spring bath every day.
Oh my God!
Mr. Kamise, you're very familiar with hot springs there.
It's nice.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Don't make me wait.
I went to Hokkaido... where there's a frozen lake.
They built a village where they could have hot springs during that time... and they pulled in sound to create a snowy landscape.
I don't know if it's the concentration or the nutrition, but it's super warm.
It's coated with a good hot spring water, you know, so it's not cold at all, even though it's cold, even though it's a little bit slippery.
It was really nice.
It's a village that only opens when there's ice.
That's right.
It's a very nice place.
And Mariko?
I went to Hokkaido a few years ago.
I went to Hokkaido with Ayaka a few years ago.
We went to a hot spring where we could see the stars and there was snow.
That would be amazing.
I'd love to be able to stretch out and touch the snow.
I'd love to be able to see the stars.
That's great!
Did you and Mariko make it to Hokkaido?
Are you okay? Mariko, I think I'll be okay.
I think I'm in danger, Master.
What if you lost your ticket or something?
I'm sure he'll be fine.
But Mag got us a hotel and everything.
Maybe an adult did it.
Your mom, an adult...
Or someone from Stardust.
Wow.
Well, well, well...
That's what I'm talking about.
Well, I guess we'd better get started on the live feed.
Oh, it's already done.
We're still doing it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I feel like I'm being watched.
Like a cheat sheet.
Like they give you a memo and you read it.
I just saw the way they put it out.
It's like they give you a bunch of pamphlets and you read them.
Just this.
That's it.
That's why.
Let's do puzzles together during the summer vacation.
Puzzles.
Everyone bought a puzzle.
And then we had them do a puzzle version of that one over there.
But now we're still receiving a lot of puzzles.
We are still receiving quite a lot of submissions.
We are still accepting submissions, and we are still accepting submissions.
What a wonderful work!
I think we will probably select one winner each.
For example, the Eiji Oba Award
Who gave you this award?
He probably received it under a pen name, not his real name.
We would draw a portrait of the person and send it directly to him or her.
It's amazing, because wouldn't you all like to have your face drawn by this person?
And since he's going to write it, I'm sure he'll look terrible in his own picture. I'm good at drawing people, too, you know.
I'm sure you're not the only one who's good at drawing, but that's not the same thing.
I know that there was a deadline, wasn't there?
We're still waiting for you, so please keep working on it!
So, that's all for now.
Thank you very much for joining us again this week!
Thank you very much.
I know it's been hot and cold here, but please take care of yourselves.
Please take care of yourselves.
That's right.
It's really cold in the morning, isn't it?
But it's hot during the day.
I know. I wish it wouldn't be that way.
How are you all doing?
You seem fine.
You look fine.
I couldn't speak at all.
I don't speak Japanese.
Oh, but there are a lot of people who have sent puzzles.
Thank you very much.
I'll take a look at them.
That's great. I received a Devil's Charge, too.
Unifi from Zadar, Mariko from long time no see, happy birthday soon!
Mariko, it's already October, isn't it?
It's your birthday month, isn't it?
So you're having a birthday party?
Yes, on the 29th.
I'll be there.
I'm going to see Mom and Dad.
It's been a year.
It's been a year since then?
It's been a year since then.
There it is.
Mariko's father had a very impressive face.
She said she remembered him.
I wrote it from that memory.
I said, “He looked like this, right?
Mariko said, “You don't look like him at all.
It's totally different.
But in my head, I already have this image of my father.
If you watch the film, you'll see...
He's holding a cotton swab.
He's holding a cotton swab, right?
No, no, no.
He's not holding a cotton swab.
I think he's holding a cotton swab in a commercial.
He has a very distinctive face.
Oh, great. A lot of people are saying they're going to the live birth or they got tickets.
Oh, that's it. That's it again.
I'm going to be at the bar with the Marika people.
That's right.
We're going to talk about how great Mariko is.
Maybe we'll have a meeting with a hot belt.
It's been a year.
That's fast!
Oh, my God.
Well, well, well, well, don't mention it.
See you next week at 8:00 a.m.?
8:00 p.m.
I'll see you next week at 8:00 p.m.
Thank you very much for this week.
Thank you very much.